Welcome to Udacity.
欢迎来到 Udacity
My name is Sebastian Thrun.
我叫塞巴斯蒂安 - 特伦
I'm the founder of Udacity.
我是 Udacity的创始人
I'm so pleased you've chosen to walk with us.
我很高兴你能和我们一起走
Our mission at Udacity is to power your career for the world's best tech education.
我们在 Udacity 的使命就是为你的职业生涯助力世界上最好的科技教育
Tech is transforming the world from
科技正在改变世界
artificial intelligence to Cloud to mobile if you're curious about
如果你好奇的是人工智能到移动到移动
it and you want to power your own career and get better and
你想让自己的事业发展得更好
better via the team that's on your site every day,
每天都在你的地盘上
every night to make you successful.
每一天晚上都能让你成功
So welcome to Udacity,
欢迎来到 Udacity
and I can't wait to see where this journey will take you.
我迫不及待地想看看这趟旅程会带你去哪